Tom, is that you?
I haven't seen you in ages.
Anna, wow, it's great to see you.
How have you been?
I've been good.
I've been at the university for six months now.
What about you?
Are you a student here?
No, actually, I've worked here since 2023.
I didn't know you were a student here.
Yeah, I moved to the city last year.
How long have you lived here?
I've lived in the city for about five
years now.
I moved here in 2020.
It's been very busy, but I've really enjoyed
it so far.
I agree.
The city is very chaotic, but I've also
found lots of great cafes, museums and art
galleries.
That's awesome.
There are heaps of opportunities here, and I've
met so many interesting people in the city.
I've made some really good friends here, actually.
I'm so happy for you.
We should catch up sometime.
I'd love that.
What time suits you best?
Midday is the best for me.
That way I can avoid commuting during rush
hour.
Works for me.
I'll text you next week and we can
organise a coffee or something.
Awesome.
I'm happy we've met again after so long.
Me too.
Anyway, I have to run.
Talk to you next week.
OK.
Bye, Tom.