Many people live in cities because there are
more jobs, schools and opportunities.
But life in the city is fast-paced
and busy.
Cities are full of offices, shops, tall buildings
and sometimes even skyscrapers
like in New York, Seoul or Dubai
The streets are often crowded with people and
there is usually a lot of traffic.
To travel around, people often use public transport
like buses, trains or trams.
In London, for example, many people take the
underground.
In Melbourne, the trams are famous.
But some people prefer to drive or cycle
like in Amsterdam.
During peak time or rush hour, public transport
is very full and the roads are congested.
This often causes traffic jams.
However, in the city, you can find almost
anything.
There are supermarkets, cafes
and restaurants with food
from many different countries.
In Paris, there are cafes on almost every
corner.
And in Bangkok, you can eat street food
at night markets.
There are also bars, clubs, museums
and art galleries.
But it's not only shops and traffic.
Cities also have parks and green spaces, like
Central Park in New York or Hyde Park
in London, where people can relax, exercise or
meet friends.
There are also many cultural events like concerts,
football matches and festivals.
In Rio de Janeiro, people celebrate Carnival.
In Berlin, there are music festivals
all year round.
There is always something to do.
On the other hand, life in the city
can be stressful.
There is often a lot of noise, pollution
and heavy traffic.
So, city life is exciting and full of
choice, but it also has problems.
What about you?